Finding Aid for the Elizabeth Vann Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- PHOTOGRAPHS IN THE COLLECTION
  - (Box 48)
    - Class pictures, maps (Box 48)
1924: Apr. 18, 19, 20, 21, 23, 25; July 8, 9, 12, 15, 16, (l)n.d.; Oct. 6, 8, 9, 13, 15, 18, 19(2), 22, 29, 30, (l)n.d. F 3.
1925: July 21, 23, 24, 25, 27, 31; Aug. 10, 12, 14, 16, 19, 20, 26, 28, 31; Sept. 2, 3; Dec. 5, 8, 13. F 4.
1926: Jan. 4, 7, 9, 13, 17, 20, 21, 25, 27; Feb. 3, 5, 7, 10, 13, 16, 17, 21, 23; June 17, 21, 23, 25; July 3, 6, 9, 12, 13, 17, 20, 29, 30; Aug. 1, 3, 4, 6, 7, 9, 10, 13, 22, 25(2), 31; Sept. 2. F 5.
1926: Nov. 8, 10, 11, 12, 13, 15, 16, 18, 20, 22, 24, 27, 29; Dec. 1, 6, 14(2), 19.
1927: Jan. 12, 18, 21, 25, 28; Feb. 2, 8, 10, 15, 19, 21, 27; Mar. 5, 9, 14, 16, 21, 28; Apr. 3, 6, 10, 14, 16, 22, 26, 29; May 1, 5, 12, 15, 18(2); June 2, 5,; Dec. 13. F 6.
1928: Jan. 5, 7, 10, 14, 18, 21, 24, 27, 28, 31; Feb. 1, 2, 7, 13, 18, 27(2); Mar. 2, 6, 18, 25; Apr. 4, 10, 17, 21, 24; May 1, 24; Dec. 31. F 7.
1929: Jan. 3, 4, 7, 12, 16, 18, 20, 21, 23, 27, 31; Feb. 6, 13, 21, 26; Mar. 5, 9, 22, 26, 29; Apr. 2, 4, 7, 15, 17, 23, 25, 28; May 11, 13, 14, 16; June 29; July 2, 6, 10, 24, 29; Aug. 3, 9, 12, 14, 21, 23. F 8.
1929: Sept. 24; Dec. 12, 13, 16, 21, 24.
1930: Jan. 6, 7, 12, 18, 23; Feb. 6, 8, 12, 20, 21, 26; Mar. 1, 5, 8, 12, 20, 27; Apr. 1, 2, 6, 12, 19, 25, 26, 28, 30; May 2. 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 12, 13, 15. 16. 17. 20. 21, 26, 27; July 1, 3, 7, i-2, 17(25, 21, 23, 25, 28, (3)n.a.; Aug. 2, 12, 16, 20, 22, 27. F 9.
1930: Nov. 2, 4, 5, 6, 8, 10, 13, 14, 18, 20, 22
1931: Jan. 9, 11, 13, 15, 18, 24, 29; Feb. 8, 15, 17, 18, (15n.d., 24; Mar. 1, 5, 7, 9, 13. 21, 24, Easter; Apr. 7(2), 9, 13, 18, 23, 24, 27, 28, 30; May 5, 8, 10, 11, 12; July 5, 9, 13, 16, 22, 23, 24; Aug. 1, 7, 10(2), 12, 21, 25, 27. F 10.
1932: Jan. 12, 15. 17, 18, 19; Mar. 6, 7, 8, 12, 18, 23, Easter, 29; Apr. 3, 4; June 27; Sept. 27; Oct. 2, 7, 26. F 11.
1933: Jan. 11, 12; Mar. 3, 5, 6, 7, 9, 15, 17; July 2, 4, 6, 11, 13, 15, 21, 28, 31; Aug. 8, 9, 11, 13, 16, 20, 24. F 12.
1933: Aug. 31; Sept. 10, 24; Oct. 2; Nov. 18; Dec. 1, 21, 30.
1934: Feb. 8, 18, 23, 26, 28; Mar. 4, 5, 7, 10, 11, 15, 22, 23, 25, 26, 29, 31; Apr. 2, 6, 11, 16, 18; May 18, 25; June 23; Aug. 15, 21. F 13.
1934: Sept. 22; Oct. 3, 6, 14, 18, 25, 30; Nov. 1, 4, 11, 13, 19, 29; Dec. 6, 14(2), 21, (l)n.d., 27-Jan.9. F 14.
OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FELIX - 1935 - 1963
1935: Jan. 3,9,20, 27; Feb. 1, 10, 14, 19, 21, 26, 28; Mar. 2, 5, 14, 21, 23; Apr. 9, 11, 17, 24(2); May 2, 9, 12, 16, 18, 23, 29, 31; June 5, 6, 8, 11, 14, 16, 20, 25, 28; July 3, 11, 25; Aug. 1, 8. F 1.
1935: Oct. 30; Nov.?.
1936: Mar. 24, 26. F 2.
1937: Jan. 20, 22(2), 29; Feb. 2; Mar. 22; June ?, 13, 24.
1938: Jan. 7. F 3.
1939: Mar. 1, 5, 12, 16, 19, 23, 26; Apr. 1, 5, 6, 7, 9, 12, 16, 19, 27, 30; May 9, 16, 21, 31; June 4, 11, 25; July 9, 16, 23; Aug. 14, 19, 27, 30. F 4.
1940: Apr. 2; July 17; Sept. 5.
1941: July 10; Aug. 18, 18(Mr. Schneider); Oct. 13, 16, 18, 21, 23, 26, 27, 30; Nov. 3; Dec. 21, 22, 23, 27.
1942: Jan. 13(Dorothea Vann). F 5.
1942: July 17, 18, 20, 22, 23, 29; Aug. 4, 6, 7, 9, 12, 18, 20, 22, 26; Sept. 2, 6, 8, 9, 12, 15, 18, 21, 22, 26; Oct. 2, 6, 10, 13, 17, 20, 22, 25, 27, 29, 30; Nov. 2, 7, 9, 11, 17. F 6.
1943: Feb. 15, 23; Mar. 3, 15, 2?, 29; Apr. 3, 4, 12, 17, 20, 24, 27, 28(Mayor Soanes), 29; May 2, 7, 9, 11, 20, 27; June 2, 11, 13, 15, 16, 18, 18(Christine Deimel), 22; July 9, 29; Aug. 10, 15, 21, 25, 31; Sept. 3, 24, 28; Oct. 2, 8, 15, 19, 25, 29; Nov. 6, 13, 22; Dec. 2, 5, 7(2), 14, 16, 17, 26, 27. F 7.
1944: Jan. 2, 5, 8, 16, 18, 20, 22, 26; Feb. 1, 9, 17(2), 21, 23, 24, 25, 26; Mar. 21, 24, 25, 29; Apr. 5, 7, 12, 20, 25; May 2, 5, 9, 11, 15, 19, 30; June 6(D-Day), 12, 19. F 8.
1944: July 19, 24, 30; Aug. 4, 8, 12, 15, 20, 27, 31; Sept. 5, 11, 18, 23; Oct. 2, 9, 13, 19-20, 28; Nov. 5, 8, 11, 16, 20, 25; Dec. 1-2, 5, 7, 20, 28. F 9.
1945: (l)n.d.; Jan. 6, 10, 12, 15, 22, 28; Feb. 2, 8, 11, 12, 16, 22, 27; Mar. 6, 10, 15, 21, 22, 27; Apr. 3, 8, 17, 23, 25; May 3, 6, 10, 16, 24, 31; June 8, 13, 19, 24. F 10.
1945: July 3, 11, 18, 23, 30, 31; Aug. 7, 12, 15, 22(Dorothea), 23, 30; Sept. 14, 21, 25, 28, 30; Nov. 13. F 11.
1946: (l)n.d.; Feb. 2, 10; Oct. 25, 29.
1947: Jan. 17; Feb. 17; June 29; Aug. 3, 5, 10, 13.
1948: Jan. 11; Feb. 4, 19, 27; (l)n.d.; Mar. ?, 6, 29, 31; Apr. 2; Oct. 21, 24, 30.
1949: Jan. 15, 16. 17, 27, 31; Feb. 1, 7, 19, 22; Mar. 2, 5, 8, 10, 14, 19, 21, 23; Sept. 26, 28, 29; Oct. 4, 10. F 12.
1951: Mar. 18, 20, 24, 25, 26, 27, 30, 31; Apr. 4, 9, 12.
1952: Mar. 3, 6, 8(Dorothea), 11, 14. 15, 17, 20, 22; Aug. 5, 6, 10(Christine Deimel), 15.
1953: Nov. 7.
1954: Aug. 7, 14, 22.
1955: Aug. 3, 11, 17, 26. Oct. 27.
1957: Feb. 13; Mar. 16, 22, 26, 28; Apr. 6; Aug. 4, 9, 15, 19.
1958: Feb. 9; Apr. 25; July 3, 11; Aug. 11(Christine), 14, 16. F 13.
1960: July 4, 7; Aug. 1, 9, 16, 23. F 14.
1961: Aug. 3, 7, 9, 10, 14, 19, 26.
1962: Aug. 9, 14, 18, 22.
1963: Jan. 2; Apr. 9, Easter, 22, 24, 27; Aug. 9, 12, 14(Christine), 18, 20, 24. F 15.
OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FELIX - 1964 - 1969
1964: Mar. 13(Dorothea); Apr. 1, 6, 11(Dorothea), 13, 16, 22, 26. F 1.
1965: (1)n.d.; Feb. 15, 18, 20, 23, 24; Mar. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5(2), 7, 8, 10, 11, 12, 15, 18, 20, ?, 24, 24-25, 29; May 2, 5,; Apr.3,4,6,8,9,11,13,14(2),15,23,29(July 2, 3, 8, 12, 17, 19, 22, 26, 28, 31. F 2.
1965: Aug, 3, 5, 8, 10, 11, 13, 15, 16, 18, 21, 23, 25, 27; Sept. 1, 5, 8, 13, 15, 17, 18, 21, 25; Nov. 4, 6, 9, 15, 16, 20, 28; Dec. 2(2), 4(Dorothea), 4(Christine), 5, 9(Mrs. Grossman), 9(2), 11, 12, 14, 15, 18, 20, 22, 28. F 3.
1966: (2 pp.)n.d.; Jan. 11, 13, 17, 21, 25, 30; Feb. 3, 9, 11, 13(Christine), 18, 19, 25; Mar. 5, 8, 13, 17, 21, 26, 28, 30; Apr. 10; May 24, 27; June 4, n.d., 15, 17, 20, 22; July 9. F 4.
1966: Aug. 5, 10-12, 20, 26, 31; Sept. 5, 8-9, 16, 19, 25, 27, 29; Oct. 3, 9, 15, 20, 23, 26; Dec. 20. F 5.
1967: Jan. 4, 6, 12, 17, 18, 23, 28; Feb. 7, 10, 12, 16, 23; Mar. 4(2), 8, 14, 19, 21, 24, 27; Apr. 2, 7, 21(Dorothea); May 1, 2, 5, 14, 17, (l)n.d.(Dorothea), 27, 31(Dorothea); June 5, 7, 9, 12, 13, 17-18, 20, 21, 30. F 6.
1967: July 10, 15, 21, 27; Aug. 1, 4, 7, 12, 15, 19, 22, 25, 30, 30(Christine & Dorothea); Sept. 1, 7, 12; Oct. 27; Nov. 2, 5, 9, 15, 17, 22, 29; Dec. 6, 7, 12, 15, 17, 23, 25, 27. F 7.
1968: (4 pp.)n.d.; Jan. 2(Christine), 6, 8, 13(2), 18, 25(Dorothea), 31; Feb. 1, 9, 14, 18, 21, 23, 27(Christine); Mar. 24; Apr. 1, 5, 10, 14, 17, 21, 25(Christine), 30; June 2(Christine), 9, 13, 19, 29. F 8.
1968: July 3, 9, 14, 16, 22, 24, 26; Aug. 2, 7, 11, 18, 20, 22; Sept. 15, 20, 21, 26; Oct. 1, 5(Dorothea),7, 9(Christine). 10; Nov. 17, 18, 19, 22, 27-29(Dorothea), 29; Dec. 23. F 9.
1969: Jan. 1, 8, 23, 24, 26, 27, 28(Dorothea); Feb. 1, 2, 6, 12, 14, 17, 20, 27; Mar. 1, 5, 10, 17, 20, 26, 31; Apr. 10, 20, 29; May 3, 7(2), 19, 20, 26, 27, 31; June 2, 4, 6, 7, 12, 14, 16, 20, 21, 25, 27(Christine & Dorothea). F 10.
1969: July 1, 5, 6, 7, 11, 15, 19, 28; Aug. 2, 5, 6, 12, 15, 18, 23, 25; Sept. 3, Labor Day, 7, 8, 14, 25, 30; Oct. 2(Dorothea), 8, 19, 26, 31; Nov. 4, 6,(2), 16, 25; Dec. 4, 5, 11, 17, 27, 30, 31. F 11.
OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FELIX - 1970 - 1973
1970: Jan. 7, 11, 20; Feb. 6-7, 24, 28; Apr. 9(2), 12, 15, 26; May 1, 4, 7, 8, 9, 13(Dorothea), 16, (l)n.d., 30; June 3, 5, 9, 17, 23, 28. F 1.
1970: July 1, 2, 7, 8, 9, 20(Christine & Dorothea), 22, 24, 28, 30, 31; Aug. (l)n.d.(Christine & Dorothea), 3, 5, 8-9, 19, 23, 29; Sept. 8, 13, 17, 21(Christine), 22, 23; Oct. 4(Christine), 4, 7, 8, 17, 20; Nov. 16, 19, 23(Christine); Dec. 2, 3(Dorothea), 28. F 2.
1971: Jan. 1, 6, 14(Christine), 19, 22, 24(Dorothea), 26; Feb. 2, 12; Mar. 3(Christine),f5, 11, 14, 18-19, 20, 31; Apr. 6, 10, 14, 18, 23; May 6, 12, 22, 26. F 3.
1971: June 1, 14, 19, 20, 24, 28; July 5-6, 12(Christine & Dorothea), 12, 13, 15, 17, 23, 24, 27, 28(Dorothea & Christine), 31. F 4.
1971: Aug. 3, 3(Christine & Dorothea),9-11, 16, 17, 20, 22(;Dorothea & Christine), 24(Dorothea & Christine), 26(Dorothea), 26, 31(Dorothea); Sept. 11(Dorothea), 14, 21, 24, 26, 28, 29; Oct. 5, 26; Nov. 3, ?(Dorothea), 11(Dorothea), 15, 17,(Dorothea); Dec. 9, 29. F 5.
1972: Jan. 3, 7, 14(Dorothea), 21, 27; Feb. 4, 6, 13, 19(Dorothea), 22, 23; Mar. 7, 11, 24-25, 29; Apr. 19, 30; May 6(Dorothea), 11(Dorothea), 20, 25, 28; June 2(2), 13, 17, 20,2/23, 26. F 6.
1972: July 3, 9, 12, 15, 20, 24, 27(Dorothea), 28-29, 30; Aug. 3-4(Sheppy Vann), 8-9, 10, 16, 25(Dorothea), 25, 30; Sept. Labor Day(Dorothea), 7, 22, 27; Oct. 3, 24, 27; Nov. 5, 12, 21, 29; Dec. 6, 8(Dorothea). F 7.
1973: Jan. 2, 10, 14, 23, 25, 29, 31; Feb. 6, 7, 10, 13, 14, 16, 17, 23, 26; Mar. 8, 25, 29; Apr. 2, 5, 8(phone call), 8, 20; May 5, 7, 14, 26. F 8.
1973: June 2, 20, 29; July 11-13, 22, 27; Aug. 3, 6, 8, 26, 28, 29; Sept. 2, 5, 7, 8, 18; Oct. 4, 5, 13(Dorothea), 14, 18, 23; Nov. 9, 19; Dec. 5, 28-31. F 9.
OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FELIX - 1974 - 1977
1974: (2)n.d.; Jan. 25; Feb. 3, 10, 13, 17, 28; Mar. 6, 11, 25, 31; Apr. 5, 17; May 1, 7, 13, 25, 31; June 7, 14, 15. F l.
1974: July 9, 11, 13, 25; Aug. 4, 6, 8, 10, 11(Dorothea), 16, 21(Dorothea); Sept. 5, 7, 10, 16(2),; Oct. 4, 12, 14(Dorothea), 17, 20, 30; Nov. 6, 7, 24; Dec. 9, 14-15, 20(Dorothea), 27, 31. F 2.
1975: (l)n.d., (2pp.)n.d.; Jan. 19, 23; Feb. 3, 8, 23, 26; Mar. 15, 21(Dorothea), 24-27, 29; Apr. 5, 8, 9, 12, 15, 28. F 3.
1975: May 1, 8, 21, 28(Dorothea); June 17, 26; July 6(Dorothea), 7, 10(Dorothea), 11, 12, 15, 18, 22, ?; Aug. 11, 16, 23, 31. F 4.
1975: Sept. 2-3, 4, 11(2), 16-17(2), ?, 25, 29; Oct. 2(Dick & Sheppy Vann), 4, 23, 27, 29; Nov. 3, 7, 22; (1) n.d. Dec. 3-4, 4(phone call), 9, 12(phone call), ?, 21(phone call), 22, 25(phone call), 27. F 5.
1976: Jan. 1-3, 6, 8, 15, 18(phone call), 20, 24; Feb. 4, 7-8, 12, 18, 20, 29; Mar. 15, 26, 31; May 11-12, 19. F 6.
1976: June 3, 5, 11, 12, 17, 28; July 3, 7, 8, 12, 18, 19, 22, 27, 29; Summer; Aug. 5(2), 11, 13, 13(phone call), 17, 21-22, 26-27. F 7.
1976: Sept. 4(phone call), 8, 12(phone call), 18; Oct. 14, 19, 24-27, 31; Nov. 8, 13, 16, 19, 23; Dec. 1, 7-8, 13. F 8.
1977: Jan. (5 pp.)n.d., 7, 17; Feb. 6(phone call), 13(phone call), 16, 18, 23; Mar. 1, 3(phone call), 5, 14(phone call), 15(phone call), 27(phone call). F 9.
OUTGOING CORRESPONDENCE TO FRIENDS
Bingham, Ray and Emma
1965: Feb. 18; July 4, Aug, 8; Sept. 7, 21; Dec. 10.
1966: Jan. 25, 29; Feb. 10, 22; Mar. 14, 16, 31; May 16, 27; June 7; July 16; Aug. 21; Oct. 2, 6; Nov. 7.
1967: Jan. 28; Feb. 25; Mar. 20, 21; May 13, 28; July 20; Nov. 11; Dec. 8.
1968: Jan. 9; Feb. 12; May 4,11; Aug. 5; Sept.
1969: Feb. 6; Mar. 2; Apr. 10; July 8,16; Sept. 10; Oct. 11; Dec. 10. F 1.
1970: Jan. 18,26; Feb. 8; Mar. 19-20; Apr. 12; May 8,17; June 21; July 9,22; Aug. 30; Sept. 15; Oct. 21.
1971: Jan. 2; Apr. 4; Aug. 25; Sept. 16.
1972: Feb. 13; May 13; July 24; Oct. 11; Nov. 17.
1973: Aug. 27.
1974: Apr. 23; Sept. 16,17; Oct. 19; Dec. 30.
1975: (l)n.d.; Jan. 17; Mar. 28; Apr. 1,8; May 5,21; Aug. 5,15; Aug. 5,15; Sept. 14; Nov. 15,19; Dec. 21.
1976: Feb. 1; Sept. ?; Oct. 11. F 2.
OTHER FRIENDS
1908: Aug. 31(Theta Sisters).
1910: Sept. ?(Julia F. Smith), 8(Saidee Jarrell), 8(Maud Sanders Tyler).
1918: June 17(Mrs. Willard Shrewsbury).
1924: Oct. 11(Mrs. Kelly).
1928: Nov. 18(Saidee Jarrell).
1934: Mar. 15(A.C. Baillie).
1936: Oct. 5(A.C. Baillie), 6(A.C. Baillie).
1955: Dec. ?(David & Myrtle, Jean & Kenneth).
1956: Mar. 9(Frank Denney).
1958: Feb. 6(Grace).
1962: Aug.4, 10(M. Virginia Dabney).
1963: Feb. 12(William Caldwell).
1965: Jan. 12(Inez Anderson).
1967: Aug. 26(Roger).
1969: Feb. 16(Nora & Helen Thurman).
1971: May 28; July 28; Nov. 10(all to Suzanne Meyer).
1972: Mar. 27(Charles Long).
1973: Feb. 4(Bob Hirst); July 4(Mrs. Shepard), 20(James Stahlman), 21(James Stahlman); Aug. 6(James Stahlman). 29(Chuck & Ella Dowds); Sept. 27(Mary & Kathleen Bond), (l)n.d.(Bonds), 28(Helen Eckert); Nov. 3(Bob Hirst), 27(Costen Harrell). Aug. 29(Chuck & Ella Douds).
1974: Aug. 24(Viola); Nov. 4(Mary Puckett). Aug. 24,27; Sept.2 (all to James Stahlman), 16(M/M Meyer).
1975: Jan. 25(Helen Orne); Feb. 17(Gladys), 17(Nora); Jan.23(Meyer) Mar. 19(May McAlister). F 3.
1975: Sept. 21(Jane Sutherland).
INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE INDEX
ELIZABETH CHAPMAN DENNY VANN PAPERS
Correspondence is listed alphabetically. Folder is indicated by the abbreviation F.
INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE FROM FAMILY (EXCLUDING EUGENE AND FELIX VANN)
BOX 14
A
Allen, Brad. 1975: May ?. F 1.
Anderson, Inez(Mrs. Holger). 1962: Oct. 30. 1964: Jan. 7. F 1.
Aron, Edith Slosson(Mrs. Ivan). (2)n.d.. 1957: Mar. 21(medical report). 1967: Mar. 24(wedding announcement). F 2.
B
Best, Jean Denny(Mrs. Andrew). 1973: Dec. 15. F 3.
C
Chapman relatives:
Davis, Louise & Hugh. 1967: Apr. 20. 1974: Oct. 4, 30. F 4.
Heath, Betty Lowndes(Mrs. Clyde). (l)n.d.. 1960: May 15; June 15; June-July; Dec. 27. 1973: Apr. 21; Sept. 24. 1974: Feb. 16; (l)after Apr. F 4.
Kingsbury, Duke & Helen. 1964: Jan. 14. 1973: Jan. 2. 1974: Jan. 1; Aug. 2,7. 1975: Jan. 6; Dec.?. F 4.
Lowndes, Lucian. 1955: May 24. F 4.
Medinger, Edith Lee & Bob. (l)n.d.(Louise & Hugh Davis). 1965: ?. F4.
Ryan, Beth & Emmett William. 1973(wedding announcement), (l)n.d. F 4.
Turner, Edith V.B. Chapman. 1965: Jan. 20. F 4.
Cobb, Katharine Denny(Mrs. Ed). (2)n.d.; 1973: Nov. 19. 1975: Mar?; July ?. F 5.
D
Deimel, Christine Schwartje(Mrs. Richard. (2)n.d.; 1935: ?; Aug. 10, 17, 19, 30. 1955: Sept. 20. 1966: June 17. 1970: July 18; Aug. 28. 1971: May ?; July 18. F 6.
Denny relatives: Cheney, Irene Denny. (l)n.d. F 7.
James, Donald Denny & Mary Bell. 1953: ?. 1965: Feb. 22, 23. 1968: Nov. 14. 1973: Oct. 26; Dec. ?. 1974: July 8, 8(to Edith); Oct. 6. 1977: Apr. 10(to Edith). F 7.
James, Donald. 1968: resolutions from the Rotary Club and the Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas, at death.
Granger, Laurie(foster daughter). n.d.(graduation invitation). 1974: ?.
Lothrop, Marguerite James(Mrs. Everett). (2)n.d.; 1963: Jan. 6. 1964: May 27. 1965: Jan. 16. 1968: Jan. 18. 1973: Feb. 12, 15; Sept. 28; Dec. 22(to Edith), 22, 31. 1974: Apr. 3; June 15; Nov. 2. 1975: Jan. 16. F 7.
Denny relatives, continued: Partridge, Cora Cheney(Mrs. Benjamin W., III). 1964: Sept. 27. 1971: Feb. 22; Nov. 29. 1975: Apr. 12. 1976: Jan.31J-De. 1977: (son’s wedding invitation. F 7.
Partridge, Ben. 1960: Nov. 12; Dec. 29. 1964: ?. 1971: May 25. F 7.
Denny, Clifford Miller and Betty(IV). (l)newspaper clipping of Betty. (4)n.d. from Clifford. 1968: June 27(Betty); (l)n.d. 1973: ?; Aug. 2; (l)n.d. 1975: ?. F 8.
Denny, Lucy Chase Chapman(Mrs. Collins). (2)n.d; (l)n.d.(to Sister), (l)n.d.(to Mary). 1902: Aug. Ik. 1903: July 1(to Margaret); Aug. ?(to Margaret). 1905: June 13(to Lucy). 1909: Mar. 9(to Rev. Collins Denny), 17, 2?(to Rev. Collins Denny), 31(2); Apr. 14(to Rev. Collins Denny), 22(to Collins Denny, Jr.), 29(to Rev. Collins Denny); Dec. ?(to Rev. Collins Denny). 1918: Jan. 3. 1924: Apr. 25(to Rev. Collins Denny).F 9.
Denny, Rev. Collins. 1903: July 1. 1909: Feb. 13(to Rev. Felix A. Vann); Aug. 9, 9(to A.T.Thompson & Co.), 16, 23(to Mrs. Collins Denny), 30. F 10. 1913: oct.23
Denny, Collins, Jr. and Rebecca Smith. 1910: Apr. 1(to Rev. Collins Denny); Sept. 9. 1943: May 10. 1944: Feb. 26. (6)n.d. 1946: Sept. 25. 1947: June 5(to Preston Slosson). 1948: Oct. 1(to Preston), 21(to Preston). 1951: Jan. 13. 1954: Feb. 11(to Lucy), 17; July 27; Aug. 17; Sept. 9; Nov. 11. 1955: May 25. 1956: Mar. 26; July 11; (l)n.d. 1957: Jan. 26; Feb. 16(to Lucy). 1959: June 2. 1960: Aug. 4; Oct. 8, 13. 1962: Sept. 23(to Elizabeth Whitfield).1963 Jan. 2; Mar. 6; May 29. 1965: Jan. 4; May 23. 1967: Sept. 30. 1968: July 10, 17. 1969: Dec. 30. F 11
Denny, Collins, Jr. Obituaries, biographical sketches, 1964. 1964: Jan. 22 from ? to Mrs. Collins Denny, Jr. F 12.
Denny, Collins, Jr. 1932: newspaper clipping - wedding. 1962: newspaper clippings: Prince Edward County, VA schools. F 13.
Denny, Collins, III and Anne. 1954: Jan. 24(to Margaret Dixon), 24(to Edith White). 196I: Jan. 16. (l)n.d. 1964: Aug. 28(to Wm. R. Cannon). 1965: Nov. 21. F 14.
Denny, John P. 1973: Dec. 28. 1974: Feb. 3; Dec. ?. 1975: Jan. 1. 1975 - photo. F 15.
Denny, Lynn C. 1971: Jan. 6. Poem, n.d. F 15.
Denny, Mrs. James W. 1909: ?. F 15.
* Denny, Rev.&Mrs. Collins. Newspaper clippings, obituaries, biographical sketch, eulogy to Bishop E.E. Hoss. Dixon, John W., Jr. and Vivian Slegle. Invitations to an open house and daughter, Edith’s wedding, (l)n.d. (to Mother) (l)n.d.(to Dorothy Meyer), (l)n.d.(to Preston Slosson), (2)n.d. F 16. 1953: Dec. 31. 1955 Or 1956: ?(to Mother). 1955: (l)n.d; Jan. 3,4,5,10,13,16,n.d., 18,23,28. 1956: (7)n.d. (to Mother). 1957: (Dn.d. (to Mother); June 6(to Mother), Sept. 5(to Mother). 1960: Dec. 30 to Mother). Dec. ?. 1962: Jan. 2(to Edith). 1963: Apr. 17(to Edith); June 30(to Mother); (l)n.d. 1965: Jan. 18; Feb. 6; Oct. ?(to Edith). 1967: Feb. 12. 1968: Feb. 19; Sept. 12(To Edith & Roscoe White). 1§69: Dec. 8. 1970: Dec. ?. 1973: Jan. 8(to Editor, Chapel Hill Newspaper), 8, 17; Dec. ?. 1974: Jan. 14; Feb. 11; June 23. 1975: Mar. 17; Aug. 7. 1976: Feb. 26. F 17.
Dixon, Margaret Collins Denny(Mrs. John W.). (5)n.d. 1895: Aug. 19 (to Mrs. Collins Denny - mother). 18(?): Aug. 22 (to Mother). 1895: ?(Mother). 1902: Aug. 16. 1903: July 3,4,13,24; Aug. 10. 1906: Aug. 6; Sept. 28; Oct. 4,H,17(Mother), 25(Edith); Nov. 8, 23; Dec. 6. 1907: Feb. 14; Mar. 21,23(Mother),29; Apr. 5,11,25,30; May 8,16,30(Edith); Nov. 24. 1908: Feb. 20; Mar. 20. 1909: Feb. 11(Mother)(2), 15(Mother), 18(Mother); Mar. 1(Rev. Collins Denny - Father); May 17. 1910: Oct. 4. 1914: Sept 9(Mother). 1946: Sept. 2. 1947: (1)n.d.; Aug. 25,27,31. F 18.
1955: Feb. 1,6,14,15,19,25; Mar. 2,14; Aug. 25. 1956: Mar. 2; Aug. 1; Sept. 1. 1957: Jan. 10; June 21; Aug. 4; Sept. 11,18; Nov. 5, 12; Dec. 1. 1959: Aug. 23; Dec. 26. 1960: (l)n.d.; June 27; Oct. 6. 1961: Jan. 3; July 18. 1963: Jan. 22; Feb. 9(Lucy & Preston); June 3,26; Sept. 14,18; Oct. 2,14,16,21,22,29; (Dn.d. F 19.
1964: Obituaries, newspaper clippings. F 20.
Dixon, William Denny and Dorothy Taylor(Dot). 1953: Dec. 29. 1954: July 8(Mother-Margaret Dixon),14(Mother), 31(Mother); Oct. 25(Mother), 30(Mother); Dec. 27(Mother). 1955: Jan! 17(Mother); Feb. 14; Mar. 14(Mother). 1956: Jan. 12; July 1(Mother). 1957: Aug. 25; Oct. 29(Mother); Nov. 18. 1958: Feb. 10(Mother). 1961: Jan. 8(Mother), 25(Mother). 1963: Apr.12(Mother); July 7(Mother); Sept. 11. Dixon, William, continued: 1964: Sept.(Brothers & Sisters). 1965: Jan. 4; June 2. 1967: Sept 10(Edith). 1972: Jan. 18(Edith). 1974: Nov. 26. 1975: Jan. 6. F 21.
Dixon, Ricky(son). (l)n.d.(to Grandmother, Margaret Dixon). F 21
E
Eckert, Helen. 1968: May 13; June 3. 1971: June 9; July 14. 1972: Oct. 15; Nov. 9; Dec. 5,27. 1973: Jan. 15(Arthur James); Feb. 25(Dr. John Sykes); Apr. 11(Mary McGarey); May 7; Sept. 23; Dec.?. 1974: Jan.5; Apr. 10,19,28; May 3,18,27; July 21; Sept. 4; Oct. 27; Dec.?. 1975: Jan. 5; July 9; Sept. 6. 1976: Feb. 29; Mar. 7; Apr. 29; May 7,30. n.d. - poem by Helen Eckert. F 22.
Frazee, Katherine Rector. 1974: July 18. F 22.
Rector, Anna M. 1974: July 11. F 22.
F
Fearjehough, Mary Libby (Elizabeth) Wright Firestone. (23)n.d. 1944: wedding announcement. 1954: Jul. 28; Aug. 18. 1957: Jul.14,15; Aug.5; Sept.4. 1966: July 24. 1968: Jan.7. 1969: Aug.28. 1970: Sept.22. 1971: Apr.18,25. 1973: Oct.9; Dec.9. 1974: June 20: Oct.?,21. 1975: Jan.1(2); Mar.19; Apr.20,?; Dec.?. F 23.
Firestone, Michael & Beverly, n.d. wedding invitation 1968: Apr.3(Elizabeth Whitfield; (2)n.d. F 24
G
Graham, Mary Lees. (l)n.d.; 1975: May 20. F 25.
Grindall, Harry G. 1973: Apr.16.
H
Hilty, Rose(Mrs. Everett Jay). (3)n.d. 1944: birth announcement: Clyde Vann Hilty. 1960: son’s wedding announcement. F 26.
Hutsinpiller, Charlie & Lillian. (3)n.d. (Hotsenpiller)Barron, Julia T. 1959: Dec. 2 Grant, Bill & Garnet Hutsinpiller. (l)n.d. Kosan, Wilraa C. 1975: Aug.26. F 27.
K
Kitchen, Catherine Ann(Mrs. Ed). (3)n.d.; Wedding Prayer. n.d. Birth .announcement. 1970: Wedding invitation. F 1.
Krebs, Elizabeth Orne (LLbba O.K.). (31)n.d. 1963: Feb.6. 1964: June 10(Libba & Tedo). 1971: May 27; Sept.?(Elizabeth, Taddy, Mary & Dale), 18(from Dale Harrison). 1973: June 14,22; July 21; Dec.4,8(Grandma). 1974: ?; Feb.l; Apr.30; July 22. 1975: Jan.8. F 2.
1977: Mar.16 (Henry & Essie) F 2.
Krebs, June(Mrs. .Stephen 0.). (l)n.d. (Margaret). 1964: Sept.2(Lucy & Preston). F 2.
Earley, Bill. High school commencement invitation. F 2.
Earley, Libby Jean(Mrs. Bob). (5)n.d.; 1971: Dec.7. F 2.
Richardson, Beth-Anne & Jim. (4)n.d. 1973: Son’s birth announcement. F 2.
M
Maier, Tom & Mary Em. 1968: Jan.15. 1976: May 3. 1977: Mar.l. F 3.
Marshall, Virginia(Mrs. Les). (l)n.d. 1973: Dec.?(2). 1974: Dec.?. 1977: Dec.?. F 4.
Ludlow, Evelyn & Lonis, (2)n.d. F 4.
Orne Family: Charman, Edith. 1951: June 6; July 22. F 5.
Cline, Gracie(Mrs. Robert W.). (l)n.d. 1962: Mar.14. 1973: son, Craig’s commencement invitation. son, Larry’s commencement announcement. F 5.
Harrison, Mary & Dale. (3)n.d. 1971: Aug.3. 1976: May ?. F 5.
Orne, Grace A. 1951: July 13. F 5.
Orne, Helen. 1962: ?. F 5.
Orne Family, continued: Orne, Stephen W. & Margaret. (l)n.d.;(l)n.d.(Whites). 1965: Jan.13. 1969: Mar.26(Edith & Roscoe White). 1974: ?(Wedding announcement); Mar. 1,10; Oct.16. 1975: Feb.l; Sept.3; Dec.10. 1977: Feb.22. F 5.
Mercereau, Helen Orne(Mrs. Harold H.). (8)n.d. 1954: Aug.4(Edith), 12(Tedo & Libba); Oct.5. 1956: Apr.17(Edith). 1960: Nov.16. 1961: Jan.23(Kathleen & Mary Bond). 1964: May 22; June 19. 1965: Jan.8. 1972: Aug.11. 1973: Mar.30; Apr.7; June 15,21; Nov.23. 1974: Mar.l; May 29; Sept.22; Oct.10. 1975: Jan.31; Apr.24,30; June 5; Aug.22; Oct.l. F 5.
Zumdahl, Teresa(“Ted”) Orne. (l)n.d.; 1962: Apr.2. F 5.
Steve ?. 1975: Apr.26.
P
Parenti, Paul & Gladys. 1973: Dec. ?. F 6.
Parsons, Marvin. 1963: Jan.30. F 7.
Payne, Elizabeth(Betty) (Mrs. William). (3)n.d. 1970: May 1. 1973: Nov.14. 1974: May 7; Sept.27. 1975: Apr.23. F 8.
Phillips, Mary Barbour Dixon(Mrs. Harold Wesley). 1954: Jan.9; Mar.23(Libba). 1955: Jan.11. 1959: Dec.28(Mother-Margaret Dixon). 1964: June 14(Libba). 1966: Aug.24. F 9.
Eiseman, Lynn & John. 1972: Wedding invitation. 1971: (Dn.d.; Feb.9; 0Ct.3L 1974: Feb.3. F 9.
1969: V.U. graduation invitation. F 9.
Lee, Julia & Blanton. (1)n.d.(WhitfieTds). 1964: Wedding announcement. F 9.
R
Rathbun, Grace(Mrs. Ford). (l)n.d. 1972: Nov.18. F 10.
Shedd, Susan Dixon(Mrs. Joseph). (1)n.d. 1957: Dec.l(Grandma). 1961: ?(Edith). 1973: Aug.20; Sept.6. 1974: Son’s birth announcement. May 22; Aug.l; Dec.?. 1975: ?. F 11.
Slosson, Lucy Denny Wright(Mrs. Preston) (2)n.d. 1910: Mar.27(Mrs. Collins Denny). 1917: ?(Mrs. Collins Denny). 1934: Dec.9(Mrs. Tweeddale). 1937: Jan.8. 1953: May 5; Oct.25. 1954: Jan.16; Mar.8; Apr.6,24; May 4(Edith),15; June 1,15; Sept.5(Edith), 22; Oct.28(Joe Hooper & Collins), 29(Edith); Nov.1-2; Dec.l. 1956: Aug.18; Sept.13; Oct.1,17,21,25; Nov.3. 1957: Mar.28; July 12(Edith); Aug.17; Sept.5, 13(Edith), 27; Oct.12, 25; Nov.13. 1958: Jan.13-31; Feb.9-12; Apr.24; June 24(Edith); Sept.22. 1959: (1)?; May 31; June 16; July 7, 31(David & Mary Libby); Aug.8(Ingeborg Wolter), 17. F 12.
1960: Jan.16, 20; Mar.13; July 28; Aug.10; Sept.?; Dec.30. 1961: Jan.16, 20. 1962: Jan.22; Feb.?,12. 1963: July 17. 1964: Apr.16; July 3; Sept.11. 1965: Feb.5(Edith): May 17; July 2; Aug.24. 1966: Jan.21(Edith); Sept.24. 1967: Mar.l; Apr.l; Sept.29. 1969: Jan.15. 1970: Jan.25; Sept.4(2), 11. 1971: Aug.28. 1973: May 4(Flora May & Wilhelm Wuellner); Oct.29; Dec.15. F 13.
Slosson, Lucy & Preston. Newspaper clippings. F-14.
* Add: Feb.28.
S
Slosson, Lucy Denny Wright(Mrs. Preston).
Incoming Correspondence after her death in 1974:
Angelo, Dave Aug.23
Carlson, Avis Aug.23
Delta Delta Delta Oct.14
Johnson, Lucille Aug.25
McCree, William & Daphne n.d.
Payne, Grace, Jr. Sept.9
Schneider, Colby Aug.21
Stahlman, James G. Aug.23
Stephenson, Lucy Chase Aug.22
Stephenson, O.W. & Evelyn Aug.22
Outgoing correspondence from: Slosson, Preston to Family & Friends. 1974: Aug.21.
Vann, Elizabeth.